A Guide to The Papers of Clifton Waller Barrett,
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Series III: Business, Financial and Family papers of Mr. Barrett., 3 green transfer cases
  - Investments
    - Winwell Exploration Company Reports 1958-59 (Box-folder 2:41)
    - Winwell Exploration Company 1959 (Box-folder 2:42)
    - Winwell Exploration Company 1959 (Box-folder 2:43)
    - Winwell Exploration Company 1959-60 (Box-folder 2:44)
    - Winwell Exploration Company 1959 (Box-folder 2:45)
    - Winwell Exploration Company 1959 (Box-folder 2:46)
    - Winwell Weekly Reports 1959 (Box-folder 2:47)
    - Winwell Exploration Co. 1961 (Box-folder 2:48)
    - Winwell Exploration Co. 1961 (Box-folder 2:49)
    - Winwell Exploration Co. 1959, 1961, 1963 (Box-folder 2:50)
    - Winwell Exploration Co. 1961 and 1959 (Box-folder 2:51)
    - Winwell Exploration Co. 1962-63 (Box-folder 2:52)
    - Yates Drug Company, Inc. 1958-59 (Box-folder 2:53)
  - Lake Placid Club
    - A large brown paper parcel, marked "Lake Placid Club" n. d. (Box-folder 3:1)
    - Lake Placid Club 1951-55 (Box-folder 3:2)
    - Lake Placid Club 1956-58 (Box-folder 3:3)
    - Lake Placid, Work at Camp Cavendish 1957-59 (Box-folder 3:4)
    - Lake Placid Club 1955-60 (Box-folder 3:5)
    - Lake Placid Club 1959 (Box-folder 3:6)
    - Lake Placid, Waller Barrett for Attention 1959-60 (Box-folder 3:7)
    - Lake Placid Club 1960 (Box-folder 3:8)
    - A brown envelope containing Lake Placid material 1962 (Box-folder 3:9)
    - Lake Placid Company 1961-62 (Box-folder 3:10)
    - Lake Placid Club 1962-63 (Box-folder 3:11)
    - Lake Placid Club 1962-63 (Box-folder 3:12)
    - Lake Placid Stationary (Box-folder 3:13)
    - Halsey B. Morrison - Insrance at Lake Placid 1951-54 (Box-folder 3:14)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence re Lake Placid 1950-55 (Box-folder 3:15)
    - A small bag containing three coat buttons marked "S. C. Y. C." and one white poker chip with brown shamrock design (Box-folder 3:16)